{
    "title": "Football",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Best team in NFL?",
            "choices": [
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions",
                "Lions"
            ],
            "answer": 3
        }
    ]
}